var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "Except",
        "pcklId": "659",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "103",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1433",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "103",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "555",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "103",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانَ",
        "answer": "mankind",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "l-insāna",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "103",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "to the truth",
        "pcklId": "277",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "103",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "خُسْرٍ",
        "answer": "loss",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "khus'rin",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "103",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالصَّبْرِ",
        "answer": "to [the] patience",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "bil-ṣabri",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "103",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحَاتِ",
        "answer": "righteous deeds",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥāti",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "103",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْعَصْرِ",
        "answer": "By the time",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wal-ʿaṣri",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "103",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "and do",
        "pcklId": "275",
        "tlit": "waʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "103",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَوَاصَوْا",
        "answer": "and enjoin (each other)",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "watawāṣaw",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "103",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَوَاصَوْا",
        "answer": "and enjoin (each other)",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "watawāṣaw",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "103",
        "ayah": "3"
    }
]; 
export default words;